Sofia L. Martin

marts818@newschool.edu 214.912.9585

Astute student with proven time management and collaboration skills developed throughout high school, college and previous job experiences. Strong understanding of the importance of working as part of a team, learning from others and developing as a professional. Dedicated, enthusiastic, self-motivated and detail-oriented.

KEY SKILLS

- Problem solving
- Active listening
- Excellent written and verbal communication
- Time management
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Apple and Microsoft Office Suite
- Creative

- Multi-tasking
- Analytical/critical thinking
- Leadership
- Social media platforms
- Adobe Premiere, Final Cut Pro and iMovie

EDUCATION

Greenhill High School – Graduated June 2018

Activities: Captain of the girl's track and field team, AP Studio Art, 48 hours of community service

Parsons School of Design - Anticipated Graduation Date: May 2022

Current GPA: 3.85

Major: Communication Design

Anticipated Minor: Creative Entrepreneurship

PERSONAL ATTRIBUTES

- ✓ Effective communicator with appreciation for and understanding of different cultures and work styles.
- ✓ Honest and reliable with a strong work ethic; ability to undertake tasks responsibly.
- ✓ **Lifelong learner** who continuously pursues knowledge outside of the workplace to benefit the company.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Intern, Godsey Martin Law Firm

June 2019 - August 2019

- Assisted marketing department with the creation of business cards, video production, and email signatures
- Illustrated official floor plan, numbered offices and cubicles
- Performed other duties as necessary, such as cleaning offices, break room, and organizing work space

District Services Agent, Body District (Gym)

June 2017 - August 2018

- Overlooked front desk, responded to incoming calls, managed check-ins
- Sold memberships and merchandise
- Pitched sales and provided tours of the gym customized to the needs of each potential member
- Used MindBody system technology to input sales as well as information for potential members
- Drafted and distributed promotional emails to clients
- Designed posters and advertisements

Sofia Martin resume, page 2

Cashier and Server, Panera Bread

May 2016 - August 2016

- Managed register and responded to incoming calls
- Marketed new products to customers
- Cleaned tables and performed other duties as necessary

Owner, PerfCreations

January 2013 - 2015

- Designed and sold trending hair accessories on Etsy
- Photographed and posted accessories for sale
- Managed inventory, invoicing and shipping

AWARDS, HONORS, MEMBERSHIPS

- Finalist, Betsy Price High School Art Competition, artwork displayed in Fort Works Art Gallery, 2018
- Artwork featured in Montage, Greenhill's student literary art magazine, 2017
- Destined 2 Run Track Club 2016 2017
- Jack Rabbits Track Club 2015 2016
- All Southwest Preparatory Conference athlete, 2017
- National Honor Society 2014, 2013, 2012

COMMUNITY SERVICE

Greenhill Hill Guide - August 2015 - May 2018

· Provided tours to prospective students and their families

Godsey Martin, P.C - 2012 - 2018

- Assisted with toy drives and bike giveaways
- Participated in annual Dallas MLK Parade
- · Served holiday meals at HEB Feast of Sharing
- Packed gifts for Angel Tree recipients

North Dallas Community Bible Fellowship - 2016

- · Packed meals at North Texas Food Bank
- Participated in clean-up project for Douglass Community Center